Dude, apart from hospitalisation, there are many other
expenses too,
so my mediclaim does not cover the treatment of critical illness,
absolutely right, don't be surprised, I am Cool
Khaya
and Kota Health Shield is what you are
looking for, just select the plan option as per your choice
and optional benefits like daily cap hospital,
which will make it a
comprehensive health insurance plan and
yes, this plan also has inbuilt wellness benefit
which will take care of your medical emergency
and even if something happens, the
detection pay-out will be given to you,
no questions as it means 360 degree
help team, absolutely right, that is why I am saying
please search room with Kota Healthy, if you
need more information, just roll down
there, everything will be clear and remember the name
[Music]